Do you feel the
community of God king
Ah this awakening can
be really too early ah
Alas peace this stuff
is really short ah
Is a community of God king adults
Yes
I also found
Hey ! Give me quiet Wukong
I was talking to
Wukong ?
Could it be that Mr. Sun
Wukong where you are now
Yes
He came to the planet practice it
Never let him know
This trip will definitely
want to come in muddy water
That is, of course Bi Lusi
adult thing I will not say
First so be it
Bi Lusi Who ah big
Eh ... Wu ... Wukong
Ah ? Is the name you snack
You know ah ah true loss
Is a kind of very tasty snacks oh
How could that be
Look sector timid king adult
to talk to you like to know
Well you still do not know
this thing is wonderful
You say I'm actually more curious
I definitely do not say
You just are adults with
community of God calls it
I directly ask slightly ~
I do not know know
instantly moved with
Do not talk of God king of adults
say that I am talking about
Some of the gods of this world
gave birth to planets and life
Just as the community of
God king is so adults
As opposed destruction
of the planet
and the life of the
gods also exist
This time what will be the
destruction of the planet too few
Alas
Diablo Bi Lusi adults
will awake yet
Estimated to have heart
operation for some time
Why do you put Tao served ?
That Bi Lusi adults should
be very strong right
Could it be that you ...
In the end how strong it
really looking forward to ah
Stupid ... stupid !
Why ah
You do not understand
what that means !
Bi Lusi adults compared
with the past to those
of the enemy would not
be a sub- element
That was the greatest in this
world Diablo Bi Lusi adults ah
Even the community
of God king scared
he will encounter adult urinary
And God is the character of
the vagaries of destruction !
That is really interesting
world's most powerful ah
Fast Wake Bi Lusi adults
Can not sleep Zs ah
After all is not
that your own alarm
clock is set at
this time bomb you
Up alarm will no
longer prepared ...
I know I know
You can stop overslept
like last 15 years ah
If you are the mountains , then
Let me present you a sober songs
Then I began
I know I know
This time I went to
bed for 39 years it
Such a point is simply nap sleep
Time to get up , but Bi
Lusi your own set ah adults
Anyway Why do you want to
set it up at this time
I have some thing to keep in mind
On the Davis
In this time I'm sleeping
Freeza destroyed the
planet Vegeta yet
Yes spotless
Is that right
After all, it is always people
on the planet to help idiot ah
King Vegeta particular,
that very stingy ah
If damage is good
in my hands down
But that planet too far
away you say , right
Too much trouble
But Freeza is not a good bird
Arrogant guy
Next time you see him
when he also ruined it
You need not take the
trouble to do this shot
Freeza has been overthrown
That someone you
can defeat Freeza
You wait
This scene seems familiar eh
This guy is backing ?
Is Saiyan
He not only called the Monkey
King is also the name Kakaluote
Saiyan Vegeta planet together
with destruction not yet
Mostly destroyed
But there are a few occasional
went live on other planets
Incidentally, of which
there are Prince Vegeta
Saiyan hair is not black it
Anyway true deficit
Saiyan can lick Freeza ah
In recent years Saiyan
Repair seems to transform into a
Super Saiyan had the ability to
That is what ?
Super Saiyan ...
Super Saiyan
Super Saiyan !
So ah
The original length so ah !
What you say
That ... Super Saiyan ...
Uh ... Super Saiyan
GOD!
I 've seen in my dreams !
I'm in a dream with
a long into this
Called " Super Saiyan
God " guy fought !
You still do not understand it
It is foreseen dream
Pre · knowledge · Dream
Dream?
Bi Lusi adults accuracy rate may
be too high to predict dream ah
Before you that " here we have
moved idol " did not dream of you
You dare not underestimate me ah
Better come with me Weiss
Prophecy fish
Prophecy fish do
I just walk it in how it
You said it 39 years ago
" After 39 years there
will be my enemies ."
I said to you
You say ah
That even say it
You see the fish prophecies and
predictions predict
my dream match it
My enemies ' Super
Saiyan God " appeared
Feeling a little do not fly ah
Anyway it 's hard
to imagine there
will be enemies
Bi Lusi adults do
Even if this argument prophecy
fish enemies exaggerated
But there is an interesting
guy in short it appears
So this time I was up early
The original is such a thing ah
So you want to see Saiyan them?
Of course
I must find out "
Super Saiyan God " ah
" Super Saiyan God " do
This name can be
really exaggerated
Actually kind of feeling weak
Found
Surviving Saiyan mostly in
4032 - Planet Green -877 No.
In that on a planet called Earth
seems to have five Saiyan
Earth ?
Never heard what on earth ah
But one
Saiyan that beat Freeza
Wang Xing, now seems on
the northern boundary
Saiyan king in circles
on the site ?
Strange ah
Davis long to get there
About 26 minutes
A set of television
animation so long you
Really far ah
Well no way
It barely trip
Then we start it
Bulma wish you
Happy Birthday !
And so on !
Eh not come ?
Why do we seek to
choose this time to go
over there king adult
industry practice ah
That guy is such
Really I told him
six months ago , ah
Eh , Mr. Vegeta it
Seems to exercise
Saiyan really is a virtue
Every time I come Boomer 's
birthday party had
fat a 5,6 kg ah
Yes ah I know
Saying Bulma
This in the end is how
old your birthday ah
You really rude ah
How could I say this to you
BINGO prizes Assembly castles
and aircraft you really have
Really ah If you
find it troublesome
money can also be replaced
Really worthy of the
world 's wealthy
Wukong is really light BINGO
meeting reveal a face arraignment
Bulma prizes it has
little Huangdie
No
Goku ! Great ... that something !
To come ! To come here !
Do you want to come
over eh Boomer
Not !
Is Bi Lusi adults
Diablo Bi Lusi adults
it is to come here
I did not feel ah
You will not understand
the breath of the gods
Well, be careful not to
listen to me foolish ah
Say nothing the matter
Good !
Really worried ah
Wukong Tibet to my house !
Why
Fast !
What was quick fast
Hurry !
OK, OK
Why exactly is
Why Bi Lusi adults to come here
Why
Oh Bi Lusi adults
You how come ah
Welcome afar
Long time no see ah
Northern boundary of the king
But speaking
Your planet can be
really small ah
Extremely sorry my house
shabby really sorry
This is because after
the destruction of
previously Bi Lusi
adults only smaller ah
Hide and seek to vent their
anger because of lost time
And this I do for you eh
By the way ...
Bi Lusi Adult Forum
Search here ah why you
I find there's a
little thing Saiyan
Bad !
Come out
Really sorry
Goku ! Give Bi Lusi
adults greeting
Hello ! I called Gordon ...
Fool
I knew you'd say that
You Laodabuxiao give
me a good hello ah
Well you ... you
I called ... not
My big name Monkey
Early
Saying that I have
something to ask you
That ...
Super ...
God is Super Saiyan
Right right
Do you know who called
Super Saiyan god do
Super Saiyan God ?
Ordinary Super Saiyan I do know
That what God I do
not understand.
I have not heard
I am also the first time I
heard that Super Saiyan God
Ah eh
I heard Davis said
You overthrown Freeza ?
Freeza ?
Ah indeed I win the
See you now feel that
we should beat ah
You will then hear empowerment
ah transfiguration
Become a Super Saiyan
It is true that you heard deficit
But heard God do Super Saiyan
Davis
That is called the
earth planet Vegeta
prince could become
a Super Saiyan do
Yes, there are other
three individuals
Seem to be able transfiguration
You could be so clearly ah
All can do this a
little suspicious ah
Then I went to the Earth it would
be able to ascertain the twelve
Bi Lusi adults ... than ...
I think other people should
not know the Messiah
Personally do not know how to ask
I went to a trip to the earth bar
That ...
You that it will not destroy it
If I did not have bad mood
I said ...
You ... not ...
I heard that you are very
great Bilu Si adults
Can I show point to look ah
You want to see my power?
How to see ?
Can look like the next
contest with me about
Wukong give me enough is enough
I have lived many years in a row
Or the first time so
interesting to hear the lines
Well you are quite confident
Or just a fool for going
For he is a fool !
He was just a fool
Alright
Then you put your
horse over it fully
3Q! Right
Thank You
But I started going all out
something wrong with it
If you are injured
But do not get angry
ah destroy the planet
I guarantee
Good Come
Then
This is the first Super Saiyan
Then Super Saiyan 2 !
This is the strongest !
Super Saiyan 3 !
Fear ah Bob Andrews !
Alas This scared me
It seems it does not boast
Oh is not it
Should I change back to two ah
This trip does not have to
Go ahead
You look down on me ah well !
That way it
OK
Goodbye friends northern
boundary of the king
Still alive ah big idiot
This can not be forgotten for a
The importance of
early to tell Vegeta
I am the king Vegeta sector
Community Wang you
find me something
You listen well I am going to say
Diablo Bi Lusi adults
immediately to your side
Diablo ?
I seem to have heard that name
In short even adults
to come unto Bi Lusi
Absolutely ... absolutely can
not talk to him yourself
Otherwise, the whole
earth will be destroyed
Destroy the earth ?
Wukong overconfident results
are easily overthrown
What did you say !
Kakaluote he ...
Become a Super Saiyan 3 Goku
Was beaten twice already dying
You said just a couple of ...
Come on the Earth's fate
is in your hands up
Really amazing
World, but there are
still such a guy
" Super Saiyan God "
is called the bar
Vegeta finally come ah
Why your wife birthday rare
still wearing battle dress ah
How is it so melancholy
Is it because your dear wife old
and a one year old so hit it too
Saiyan nice ah
Are not old
Shut up !
What closed mouth ah hum
This is how it is such
a mess why I mind
I Vegeta adults actually
will tremble with fear
Really
Diablo Bi Lusi
I definitely saw where he
Yo you are right prince Vegeta
Both have grown ah
You often say that " gas "
It seems God is invalid ah
Think of it yet
Think of it ...
Last met when you
were a youngster it
Do not remember
Your father King Vegeta
But some ah me a good reception
Diablo Bi Lusi
You ...
Community Wang said is true
This guy is extremely
tricky tricky
It seems that you seem to do
anything interesting
gatherings ah
And it particularly tasty flavor
Ah this is my wife's
birthday party
Your wife do
Then I can get a good Poke
Bi Lusi adults
Right down to business
almost forgot
You ah
Have you ever heard the god
of Super Saiyan name ah
Super Saiyan God ?
Do not know
Sure enough, it was a
mistake to predict dream
I can not be wrong !
Doraemon wrong DEK
I'm a little uncomfortable
Ah Vegeta you were asking
your wife to shut up ah
This is
This is Mr. Bi Lusi
My name is Travis
You do acquaintances
Hello my name is Bulma
I was Vegeta ...
Beautiful wife
Hello Miss Bulma
Your acquaintances where
it has a good taste ah so
But people do not
look like the Earth
You are now an alien aliens
Enough of it !
I just had to suffer through
the planet Vegeta ah
To do sightseeing
If you are willing to show up
to the party together or not ah
Oh, you are welcome
Hey !
Really sorry
In fact, I have just discovered
that there are very tasty food
Please please
Go go ~
Where is it Dragonball
Should be seven are all here ah
I do not know why there is
no desire to achieve it
But for us, but a very good thing
My next wish is !
Become super rich !
Do not want to conquer the world
First, you must first
get a sum of money
I've had enough of this
life of poor people
I look too kid who did not
even hire me to work ah !
Forget
The adults but Pila Fu king ah !
Before finally let us achieve
the aspirations of the Dragon
Blame Pila Fu adults say ,
"Let me restore youth ! "
Now that we have become virtues
But can ...
Even the elderly will
soon conquer the
world does not make
sense belch fart ah
Words to say that it
has become too young
I'd saved it
Already passed the
limits of a dog's life
Do not give me crap !
Quickly find Pearl !
Then bad things that also
gave me valuable stuff
Be
Leather ... Pila Fu adults
How the
This ... this is
What ?
BINGO Assembly prize ?
This would not say ...
Which are all
Prizes do !
Castle actually will be prizes !
Amazing !
Damn guy is really a
bunch of luxury !
I see you painting flowers !
Hateful
You too were made under this
This does not in this
castle inside it
Pila Fu adults
With you !
Participation Award
turned out to be super-
senior ham Assorted
Gift ten copies !
Simply take it two or three boxes
Yahoo!
Second prize ...
This diamond is too big now !
Take away !
But this is only the
second prize ...
First prize on ...
Easy to find friends
Pila Fu adults
Collect all seven ...
seven really here , ah
Hooray ! Hooray !
Great !
Pila Fu adults
Here our desire to achieve it
Idiot
In a place like this will bring
up the ceiling collapsed Dragon
Hey you guys
There doing it
We are partners in this child
Eh my friend ?
Oh you are the children at home
Monkey speak !
Monkey ...
Monkey ?
Who is the monkey ah !
The adults are Pila Fu king ah
We 've come to steal ah
How it can be reported real name
Hey Goten
Come
Here are just funny monkeys oh
It is not a monkey !
Hey give me a quiet kid
Lesson you would like to eat
How it
Look
That quite personal hairstyle ...
I feel very familiar ah ...
This ... you !
Pila Fu adults like me !
Wow really strange
monkeys and Goua
Ah
Na this beautiful stone
girl who sent you
It is Telankesi friend
She is my girlfriend !
How powerful it like
You in a relationship right
Yes, ah , we also held hands it
Amazing ah
Also ... okay
Damn why he would be there
He has also maintained
the child, like ah !
All his fault I did not
get the Dragonball harm
Why do you laugh so disgusting
You look at it
What's this !
I confuse with diamonds
Result, they did not find
four planet was I stole !
Small dance Well done !
Thank you
And so on how to
achieve a desire ah
Do not worry Pila Fu adults
Want this thing to go back
and give us one million !
Such blackmail them just fine
The girl is Telankesi girlfriend
I do not know which
side it is inherited
Your kid really solid two ah
Well quite capable
Amazing ah
Okay
Called her over
Little master ! You just
are not flying over ah
Compared to such a trivial matter
I just try to be
brave accidentally
Say you're my girlfriend ...
Eh ... you said I was your ...
Not you !
Is it me ?
Why are you ah !
I said that this girl !
I ...
I will not tell you
this kid actor
You do not also kid actor
Eh eh ah
Sorry ah
Can you install my girlfriend
Loading your girlfriend ...
how can I do ah
Is holding hands ... like ...
Hand ... pull ...
Now the children are
too impure friends !
You can enjoy eating delicious !
Delicious !
There BINGO Assembly Oh !
Well !
Come !
You wait
Pila Fu adults ... even
if that person is a child
I can not talk to people who
first met in hand ah ...
I say you ah fact, already
it is not small !
Pila Fu adults some words to say
some words should not say ah !
Small dance on the bar
It's all delicious with BINGO
Also
Pearl took the
opportunity to win !
That feeling that you saw ah Aunt
That ... that time ...
Really the case ah
She was with that
kid together ...
I'm kind of a very bad feeling
Come
Good ... good
This is called the octopus balls
ball child can be
really interesting
Very tasty ah
Whether or soy sauce taste taste
Very good ah !
You petit dance ah
How old are you,
little dance friends
41 years old
Do not play stupid adults ah
Turtle ...
Pie ...
Gas ...
Power ...
Do not sabotage ah ...
Wave !
Mess ah
Not ah
This degree ...
But simply winning Diablo
Bi Lusi adults much
stronger than this !
Na world king of adults
It seems like just about practice
That simply can not become
a Super Saiyan 's what God
Anyway
It does not show up
Super Saiyan God
Loss I also look
forward to a bit too
I have learned a bit
although all Saiyans
If in addition to the
Monkey King and Vegeta
and earth than are
people of mixed it
And there are two or child
Next is the grand finale
of this gathering
BINGO Assembly !
Although the castle
and the aircraft
has been a very heavy prize
But to say that the most
heavy prizes or ...
Carefully optimistic about
Seven Dragonball Oh !
If you won the lottery you
can achieve any desire !
Well !
That ball like Namek
Wishing ball ah
Because if that is the
God of Earth Namek ah
I remember like the ball
ran out from the dragon to
Then all the desire to achieve it
Hey wait a minute
It is less a Dragonball ah
Four planets gone !
Oh, no
Just still in it
Na you go yet
Small dance put your phone
number to tell me ah
I did not do that fancy goods
Etc. Well
Idiot !
Not bad ...
In the move
Are your own shout out ah
The matter has now had such a
Damn !
Pila Fu adults
Hey you guys
If you do not want
to let this kid die
Give me one million !
It can also be ... 100000
There are ... What's so funny
Oh really will kill him !
Clearly said that
several kid to kill
The results we are
laughing ah how
It seems necessary to punish
Nothing
That girl is like
my son's girlfriend
Ah really boring farce
Really really really ah !
That ... that little dance
Hostages to me to shut up
Your chest hit me
This can be really
interesting ah Cabaret
Well then I have
participated in a good
Cute villain who
I can not forgive Great Saiya
Superman bad guys , oh
Gohan Well done !
Strange ah
Could it be that it is
the god do Super Saiyan
Please do not misunderstand
It was the son of Kakaluote
Just changed clothes
Little girl fast shoot me ah
This ... this kind of thing
Do not come over
Bold shoot me
This is more interesting ah
Right
It is better to shoot
a clean shot it all
This is more interesting
All full ...
Nothing the matter
He will fight all the
bullets are flying
Oh, do not fight foot
More is not gorgeous ah
Shot on face
I shoot bad guys enjoy it !
Whatever you want it !
How about bad guys
Great Saiyan know yet
powerful Superman
That guy personality
has changed ah
Not used to drinking drink bar
You guys
I thought it was the
result is genuine ah toys
This can not ah
How children could get
that kind of stuff
If the object is not
me it would be bad
Haoteng
Videl Videl are you okay
Videl !
Gohan how you can
hit his wife too !
Right ... I'm sorry !
Let me treat it
What are you doing
Watch your words
But his immortal
Immortal ?
It is true
You do a god
Cured
Thank you god
That ... you have a pregnant ...
This also confidential Hush
So ah
Gohan forbid me to drink !
Hear no
Good ... good
Thank you every day
Right ... immortals
I have flown here ah
Little itchy
Accurate
Very unhappy
It destroyed the Earth yet
A comparison of the entire
planet refurbished Well
Before creation is destroyed
Hey you guys !
Cabaret has ended
BINGO fast into a
pleasant meeting it !
BINGO!
How the ventilation
yet even Vegeta are
Happy BINGO!
The Earth is one !
Very happy place !
M ~ rice is also
very good to eat ~ ~
Happy BINGO!
Disappointed ah feel better
I did not think this guy can sing
and dance rotten at this point
Davis 's voice can be
compared to compete with the
This can be really unexpected
Well, in order to improve mood
Eat something good
Yes ah
Well, well Headshake
You guys this is not a toy beads
Oh, can not take the chaos
But you play the game
was a bit of fun
Xiela
Well, since Dragonball all here
Then it began BINGO
Are willing to give up
the dignity of the uncle
happy to discuss only
salvation ah Bi Lusi
Now safe
The rest is to keep him
leave the Earth a good mood
Great !
Some winners do
Bi Lusi adults
That is called your
pudding dessert eaten yet
It is really delicious ah Huanen
What pudding ?
Where is that
Over there
I say you
Can you give me a minute eat
Plus I was two
I have a minimum of
points on the line
Bi Lusi adults too cunning
You've eaten it
Give me !
Do not !
What did you say
All I have to eat
You have so much !
All are my !
Give me
Must not
Give me ah idiot !
You call me stupid , ah !
I want you to eat as a snack !
Bad ! Do not pay attention
to a little one !
I fire !
Etc.
Bi Lusi adults, please stop
Go and stop him fast ...
Blame you do not have to give
me a good pudding repair it
Stop
Damn ! He casually hell !
Waiting
This is really very delicious ah
What does this thing called
That ... that
This is called Sushi
'd Still rather fight with taste
Hey ! Side of the Cat People
Trick even order a pudding
Like you guys are not polite
Gotenks by me fly
you to play adult
What did you say
People on earth you probably
already tired of eating
For me it is can never
imagined unknown food ah !
Pudding !
This name sounds can be
really delicious ah !
Hello ... long-winded !
Stop it he won not your enemy
Sore ! Sore !
I'm sorry !
Although there are expected
to be tricky this guy
But really did not think
that there is such a state
Hateful
Finally finished yet
No pudding
Super Saiyan is no god
Only destroyed
Well Diablo Bi Lusi is also
a kind of honor killing
Damn your statement is
actually pleasant to the ear
Then as you wish
Really give me
enough is enough ah
Although I do not know if you are
still acquaintances who Vegeta
I am 38 years old birthday
party are a mess it !
38 years old do
How dare you
Hit me ...
Bulma !
Bastard !
Really powerful
This guy Vegeta
Finally surpass Goku yet
Take that !
How ... how the
Universal Capsule company has
in place yet large fireworks
How to
It seems that this is not
the God of Super Saiyan
Enough to destroy the
earth and then go back
Davis
Wait a moment
Eh sea urchin sushi warships ?
This is really delicious ah
I ... I do not let you do that !
Always destroy destruction yell
You can be really long-winded ah
I'm not saying you finished
Vegeta !
Davis !
You told me to do Bilu Si adults
It seems that the so-called
Super Saiyan God
As you said it was
just a silly dream
Do not let me say so many times !
Then go back to the
destruction of Earth
I know
But please wait a little longer
You ... you feel how
tuna sushi roll
Great
Anyway I seem to leave
Will this package you can
And so on !
Wukong
Goku !
Monkey !
Is you do
How the
You figure out who is
the god of Saiyan yet
That guy is still a mystery
But you do not destroy
the planet okay
I am the god of destruction
I know Bi Lusi adults
But this time you
put a horse or bar
That is to how to
Do you talk to me to fight a
I want to say it
But it is a headache ah
To be honest I think in any
case it is difficult to win you
Right !
Bi Lusi adults can not
let me gamble look ah
What
Is that the God of Super Saiyan
I'm just saying maybe ah
They might be able to change my
How change
Can you give me some time ah
On a little bit of good
Please,
Well on a little bit
Xiela
Bulma
These Dragonball to lend me oh
Alright
If you help me fix that
being polite asshole
Although the use of it on
Your mouth stinks ah
But God does that person
Oh God ?
Why ah If you the word of God
Do not order a pudding
quarreling fool !
He is no ordinary God
He is the God of the world's
most terrifying destruction
He called Bi Lusi adults
Oh strongest universe
Even the world king
of adult community
of God king scared
adults had urinary oh
Everybody
Please note that your words
If so angered Bi
Lusi unhappy adults
The solar system
will be wiped out
in minutes and
seconds between oh
Bi Lusi adults than ...
Stop it can only play
a counter- aged women
Shut
Haoteng
Goku Dragonball do
you intend to use
Come out ! Dragon !
Then carry out my wishes now !
So ah let Dragon do to prevent
him from destroying the planet
It is impossible not
Universal capsules business
The program can be really
wealthy family gorgeous ah
Wish I could achieve whatever
Well !
That ah Dragon
Do you know the God
you Super Saiyan
What is this ah
I want to ask the
same question with ah
I know
Really you know eh
Really
Confirm your genuine desire to do
No no no !
If you know it can not
bring him here to do
I can not bring him
Because it does not exist ah
God called Super Saiyan
Moment is manufactured Saiyan God
That is how
Your question really, ah
What is your wish in the end
Bi Lusi adults want us to
surrender Super Saiyan God
Bi Lusi adults ...
Bi Lusi first met adults
Tell me how to create
a Super Saiyan God
Good
Dragon is the first time
I saw such a reaction
God called Super Saiyan
There are a small part
of the last Saiyan
For the wickedness
of their fellow
citizens feel doubt
and rebellion
Then accidentally create a savior
Who savior to
unparalleled strength
At the moment it will be
those bad Saiyan to pack up
His winning time will change
back to the prototype lost power
Planet Vegeta once again in
the hands of evil Saiyan
And also the savior off track
from the legendary Silencer
That silencer Trailbreaker
legend is ...
Your story is really long ah
Do you understand yet Vegeta
Hush Shut
Five good heart Saiyan work
Another good heart to the
hearts of injected light Saiyan
He can into Saiyan God
Way I told you
Goodbye
I will retire a ...
Five good heart Saiyan ?
Impossible ah
Only such a Saiyan Gohan
and Goten two compliant
You are so rude !
Even Vegeta count
Trunks heart can be good , ah !
Like the kind of
hair is not long
Qi guy had a
girlfriend too pure a
Really old in the old-fashioned
You are not jealous ah
Yes ah BAK
Goku nor do you want to say pure
Wukong really quite pure
Is a pure fighting fool
Say that the heart is not pure
and good can be a bit subtle
Shut up ! Colored old man !
What did you say ! Dare to
speak on such a fairy !
Hastened to Super
Saiyan god born ah !
Vegeta though he had very bad
How about now
Or do bad
'd Say ah
That guy really did not
do bad things recently
Why should Kakaluote centered ah
Do not bullshit
My father has since
any changes you
Do not ... I do not know ah
Waiting friends
This is the fried
shrimp tempura do
This is also very good eat
Successful yet
Dad feels fighting strong ah
Goku finally into a god yet
Monkey quick show for us to see
Stop it Wukong
Futile battle
This level is not God
But can ...
Just because everyone's fighting
ability was promoted together a
Is so
Fighting overflow
in the appearance
of God can not be called
Oh so ah
Sure enough, ah
Always feel or beat
Bi Lusi adults
How could this ...
Listen up everybody
Recall
Is' five Super Saiyan Saiyan
hearts to inject another light . "
Saiyan required total
six people do not
So ah I was wrong
Six people ?
Short of a man ...
Vegeta on the
You do not have a
serious brother do
He was in a very distant planet
And I do not know
specifically where
You did not ask his
cell phone number you
Enough
Deficit what I thought
interesting development
Too disappointed
I've been sleepy
Quickly put to the destruction
of the earth and then go back
That ... there is one here
Videl ... there is a ?
That ... is a person to say it
Or fast become one of it
But he did Saiyan blood flowing
What are you talking Videl
Although it is a great dad
It is pure earth can ah
I do not mean Dad
That ... Videl lady 's stomach
With the baby does
Really really ...
Really ah
Gohan had wanted to scare it
deliberately did not say hop
Very good
To become a Super Saiyan god
you changed unchanged ah
Quickly
Plus Videl do it all over it
It can not do ah
have not born yet
Anyway try first
Good
Sure enough, or not do
Hey is not that unusual Wukong do
But you see the red hair
Really ah
There is not a thin point ah
See how much fighting Goku
Congratulation
Appears to be a success
I finally have the
results waiting
Really
I became a Super Saiyan God yet
What should it clear the contest
Well, put your horse over it
Okay, I got on the
OK ah If you stronger words
Well, I will not
destroy the earth
Really too thanks
How to become a Super Saiyan
God what do you think
Really surprised ah
Really surprised you
My thoughts like you
It is a good feeling
How you seem quite
satisfied with ah
A little
You do not like to be God
Ah really did not think
there is such a realm
What do you mean
It is always with me to
a realm that can not be
So do you feel dissatisfied
Ah ah discontent
How else do earthquake
You put can be really
interesting ah
You actually are
not satisfied by
the power of peers
to become God do
I'm glad ah
Although pleased
But if I did not hesitate
to everyone's effort
You can not like adults
with Bi Lusi Battle
I am not willing to ah
And why do you become a god
Because I want to play a
game of Bi Lusi adults
Catch up
Good
Regroup the
Right to become God or upset you
Yes ah
This self-esteem will
be your weaknesses
Self-esteem is really boring
Be particular about such a
thing can be rare ah Saiyan
This ... this is how the power of
Are not so
Vegeta than I had better stick
to the dignity of a much ah
Now he just abandoned it
dignity to guard everyone
I know
He did not have to abandon the
dignity of the prince to do so
It is great
I have a little respect for him
So you also give up the
dignity of God yet
Is such
Two men talking about
Goku just like in
practice accepted as ah
Words in front of me is
also very satisfied with ah
How ?
I totally did not
fight it all out
Oh Really
I have resorted to the
skill of eighty percent
Eh eighty percent
Then you can do to
keep up with my speed
How this is your real skill you
Is a real skill ah
How you play the
long-range attack
Well this is not in motion ah
Do not give me to
enjoy destroy ah
That guy is not God
Changed back to a
normal Super Saiyan
Brooklyn see it
See
If you play with me the remote
I also
As money-back guarantee
Please do not hesitate to
It was Goku's turtle
pie qigong wave
How else
This is my salute
Next, look at me so
What is it
Bi Lusi attack
Bad !
You guys
Hateful
It seems that you
have not noticed ah
What
Super Saiyan god long time to
Really
But can ...
It appears that you are god into
a Super Saiyan when fighting
Also the realm of that
layer to absorb ah
So even if you restore it
How much force did not weaken
Really great ah
Turns out to be the
story of rare talent
I can be really happy ah
Then happy now it's not your
long-cherished wish you
I can not do
The biggest problem is ...
Even so, the gap is still
very large force ah !
Then you give up the
right to surrender
What happened ?
Damn !
Goku !
Hey you just do what
Do not ... I do not know ah !
Do not know
What a funny guy
Why Why did you receive hands
Because I want you to
throw in the towel ah
I lost
I lost ah
Bi Lusi good strong ah adults
It is difficult enemy
Really worthy of
the universe first
You seem to finally understand
Diablo Bi Lusi horror of the ah
But you really have a strong
In the long history of
the struggle in so far
You are the second strongest
What second ah
Finally, I 'll tell
you that a good thing
What ah you will not
destroy the Earth yet
This can not
Because I was once a decision
on the unwavering doctrine
That ... what ?
Yonder attendants called Weiss
He is my attendants
Also my Master
Master ?
The first is that
the universe ...
It is the seventh world universe
I am a seventh Diablo universe
A total of 12 cosmic ah
Do not you think there
is a stronger guy Exist
Wukong
Goku !
Okay I'm alive
Then according to the agreed
Let me destroy the Earth.
Oh Yeah Bi Lusi adults
You destroy the Earth
it can be really small
What a pity ah
Is it because I have
no strength of it
Just wait until the next time it
is completely destroy the Earth
Bi Lusi adults
I say you
Etc. Bi Lusi adults die or not
to do When the next Diablo
Hey !
Then I can really
afford it by the
What a pity ah
Vegeta Mrs.
Eh I ?
How ... how the ah
Xuanrao some really sorry ah
Compared to this as soon
as you hit me an apology
Hold ... sorry
Hey you stupid do
If so, please invite
me to the party again
Then you have to promise
not to cause trouble , oh
Understand
Next may have to give me eat
something that is
called pudding oh
I will give you a lot
to prepare the pudding
But you can not eat too
unpalatable again oh
If I really destroy the
earth unpalatable friends
Then we can fight another
adult friends Bilu Si
Goodbye
Incredible
Yes ah
Diablo Bi Lusi
adults actually ...
No damage
Sure enough, or care
of the Monkey King
's blessing ah this
magical figure
More and more partners
Finally even the Bi Lusi
also one one of the adults
Anyway that guy really can
not measure the potential
But that was not yet
strong enemy ah
But even adults resorted
to Bilu Si Qi Cheng skill
Ah really long absence
That guy called what
Monkey
That guy and Vegeta
Maybe one day can really
become my enemies ah
Ah speaking
Because it is so delicious
So I put this thing called
sushi back to the pack
The food can be
really delicious ah
Please dipped
slightly this side of
the liquid called
soy sauce to eat Oh
This is what the green block
This is ...
Ah dishes people say
"Please to taste ."
Seems to be kind of a
thing called mustard
Seems indeed to hear him say
In the time I fought
I went to get you to drink
Let me taste
Bad
Then please sleep
for three years now
Ah Bi Lusi adults
Brush your teeth before
going to bed too ah
I know I know
Well then again
Bulma wish you
Happy Birthday !
Yo 38 years old !
Noisy died
Eat fast
You hurry
What are scary ah comparable
Hey Kakaluote
Next time I have to
change when God , ah !
You have to help me, oh well
Ah of course
But you can not try to
be brave transfiguration
Oh end they drop
Vegeta on the
Bulma was beaten when
You shouted, "My Bulma ! "
Then becomes a very
powerful Super Saiyan , ah
I feel your love , oh
I do not remember the
kind words spoken !
Can then
I think I definitely
have beat you up !
Indeed ah ah
When fighting with
the enemies next
Let him go to a good beat Bulma
Hey !
Vegeta said that words when
You should not present ah
Is instantly moved to here early
Then voyeur hiding in
the side of the bar
That ...
Monkey
Really you guys
Everybody was dangerous
when you actually hide
Sorry sorry
I just observe each operational
plan of action just thinking
But I have not thought
out what it wants
Bulma resort to slap
him twenty-three
Yes sir
Sorry I will reflect on
Turtle ...
Pie ...
Gas ...
Power ...
Wave !